# Khushboo

Contact Information: +91 8837846003, khushboo15624@gmail.com





# **Objective:**

Highly skilled software developer with 2 years of experience seeking a challenging role to contribute to the development and delivery of innovative software solutions. Committed to continuous learning and staying updated with emerging technologies to drive successful project outcomes.

## **Education:**

#### **Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science/Software Engineering**

Chitkara University, Himachal Pradesh	2018 – 2022
CGPA – 9.63	
Intermediate	
Shishu Niketan Model Senior Secondary School	2018
Percentage – 72.6%	
High School	
Shishu Niketan Model Senior Secondary School	2016

## **Technical Skills:**

CGPA - 9.0

Programming Languages: JavaScript, Java, C

• Web Development: HTML, CSS, TypeScript, Bootstrap

• Framework/s: Angular, Ionic

Database: MySQLVersion Control: Git

• IDEs: IntelliJ IDEA, Eclipse, VSCode

## **Experience:**

Intern, Translab Technologies Bengaluru (June 2021 – May 2022)

- Worked on a development project using Angular and Nebular.
- Possess knowledge of cloud networking.
- Worked on Ansible Automation.
- Deployed AWX, EFK in Kubernetes with Ansible.
- Basic knowledge of Networking.

Software Engineer, Pratishthan Software Ventures Bengaluru (June 2022-Present)

- Developing a hybrid app for a reputable multinational insurance company.
- Proficient in Angular 14, Ionic 6, and Java through hands-on Experience.
- Implemented RESTful APIs to enhance application functionality.
- Utilized HTML5 and CSS to create engaging and responsive web experiences.
- Leveraged XML to design and generate Scalable Vector Graphics (SVGs).

## **Projects:**

- **Project 1:** Front End website:
  - A Graphical User-friendly website named "Chaa-Paani" focused on food.
  - Languages used: HTML, JavaScript, CSS, Bootstrap.
- **Project 2:** Campus Recruitment System:
  - Developed a full-stack project aimed at streamlining the placement process for students and companies.
  - Languages used: Java, Java Swing, and SQL.
- **Project 3:** Calculator:
  - Created a simple phone-type calculator.
  - Languages used: CSS, jQuery.
- **Project 4:** Quiz-module:
  - Developed a quiz page that tracks scores.
  - Language used: HTML5, JavaScript.

#### **Certifications:**

- 1. VTSP Network Virtualization (2019) by VMWare Certificate
- 2. Red Hat Delivery Specialist Virtualization. Certificate
- 3. Red Hat Delivery Specialist OpenShift Container Platform Support Certificate
- 4. 5-star Ranking on Hacker Rank
- 5. Earned a badge by IBM for completing a course on data science Badge

#### **Extra-curricular Activities:**

- Vice president for University Communication Club S.U.F.Y
- Member of University Math Club-Math Pirates.
- Participated in a research presentation competition.
- Participated in a Hackathon presented by Accenture.
- Solved 100+ questions on LeetCode.

#### **Additional Skills:**

- Strong problem-solving and analytical skills
- Excellent communication and collaboration abilities
- Self-motivated and eager to learn new technologies
- Ability to work effectively in a team-oriented environment